{
  "id": "MA3173",
  "introvideo": "src",
  "GameType": "SelfDefine",
  "IntroText": {
    "Type": "PlainText",
    "Content": ""
  },
  "GameConfig": {},
  "Questions": [
    [
      {
        "Question": "84÷7=12",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "84",
            "operand2": "7"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "12",
              "operand2": "7"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "78÷6=13",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "78",
            "operand2": "6"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "13",
              "operand2": "6"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "45÷3=15",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "45",
            "operand2": "3"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "45",
              "operand2": "3"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "86÷2=43",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "86",
            "operand2": "2"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "43",
              "operand2": "2"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "72÷4=18",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "72",
            "operand2": "4"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "18",
              "operand2": "4"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Question": "540÷5=108",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "540",
            "operand2": "5"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "108",
              "operand2": "5"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "135÷3=45",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "135",
            "operand2": "3"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "45",
              "operand2": "3"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "804÷4=201",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "804",
            "operand2": "4"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "201",
              "operand2": "4"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "336÷3=112",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "336",
            "operand2": "3"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "112",
              "operand2": "3"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "318÷6=53",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "318",
            "operand2": "6"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "53",
              "operand2": "6"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Question": "85÷6=14...1",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "85",
            "operand2": "6"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "14",
              "operand2": "6"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "84",
              "operand2": "1"
            },
            "answer": 85
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "88÷7=12...4",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "88",
            "operand2": "7"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "12",
              "operand2": "7"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "84",
              "operand2": "4"
            },
            "answer": 88
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "93÷5=18...3",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "93",
            "operand2": "5"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "18",
              "operand2": "5"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "90",
              "operand2": "2"
            },
            "answer": 93
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "90÷8=11...2",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "90",
            "operand2": "8"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "16",
              "operand2": "4"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "64",
              "operand2": "1"
            },
            "answer": 90
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "65÷4=16...1",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "65",
            "operand2": "4"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "16",
              "operand2": "4"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "64",
              "operand2": "1"
            },
            "answer": 65
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Question": "290÷4=72...2",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "290",
            "operand2": "4"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "72",
              "operand2": "4"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "288",
              "operand2": "2"
            },
            "answer": 290
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "169÷6=28...1",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "169",
            "operand2": "6"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "28",
              "operand2": "1"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "24",
              "operand2": "1"
            },
            "answer": 169
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "170÷8=21...2",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "170",
            "operand2": "8"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "21",
              "operand2": "2"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "42",
              "operand2": "2"
            },
            "answer": 170
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "188÷9=20...8",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "188",
            "operand2": "9"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "20",
              "operand2": "8"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "180",
              "operand2": "8"
            },
            "answer": 188
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "164÷7=23...3",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "164",
            "operand2": "7"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "23",
              "operand2": "3"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "161",
              "operand2": "3"
            },
            "answer": 164
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Question": "429÷4=107...1",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "429",
            "operand2": "4"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "107",
              "operand2": "1"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "428",
              "operand2": "1"
            },
            "answer": 429
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "716÷7=102...2",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "716",
            "operand2": "7"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "102",
              "operand2": "2"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "612",
              "operand2": "2"
            },
            "answer": 716
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "347÷3=115...2",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "347",
            "operand2": "3"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "115",
              "operand2": "2"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "345",
              "operand2": "2"
            },
            "answer": 347
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "904÷6=150...4",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "904",
            "operand2": "6"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "150",
              "operand2": "4"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "600",
              "operand2": "4"
            },
            "answer": 904
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Question": "606÷5=121...1",
        "questionBoard": {
          "type": "division",
          "mode": "display",
          "operands": {
            "operand1": "606",
            "operand2": "5"
          },
          "unitType": "Number"
        },
        "answerBoard": [
          {
            "type": "multiply",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "121",
              "operand2": "1"
            }
          },
          {
            "type": "add",
            "mode": "checkAnswer",
            "unitType": "Number",
            "operands": {
              "operand1": "605",
              "operand2": "1"
            },
            "answer": 606
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  ]
}
